{
    "id": "fb719c2c898549c2a0cca062a9eec215",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns And Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ".......................... she said made no sense to me.",
            "description": "What means the thing that which.",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "That",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a14c44960e764bb091a612702aa81daa"
        },
        {
            "question": "All ............................ I want is something to eat.",
            "description": "The relative pronoun that can refer to things. It is common after all, any etc.",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "feccdddeb0b24b69889d93cc4444bd4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can give you ............................. you need.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "efe29bbba74f45258cefc50b1d4b35f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She got married again after two months, ................................. made her parents angry.",
            "description": "Which can modify an entire clause.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24454b4a0f9249859f22c12e3241411a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has acted in a movie ............................. name I don't remember.",
            "description": "Whose replaces pronouns like his, her, its. He has acted in a movie. I don't remember its name. He has acted in a movie whose name I don't remember. ",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "311b401fe2544cf6882aec82b0e821c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has acted in a movie the name of ............................ I can't remember.",
            "description": "The name of which means the same as whose name. ",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8bec8b21a9a3491081e5c20cfc07d42d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He married a highly successful business woman ............................... you may have heard of.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "828db60cb39c4896bb96f4d92a5f3217"
        },
        {
            "question": "He married a rich heiress of ............................... you may have heard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cefa2126853b42068353d125f944b777"
        },
        {
            "question": "You know Mary ................................. mother is a writer?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whose",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7dfb1cea28fa40b28daf7d17f13bf574"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to see some old neighbors .............................. children I used to play with when I was small.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6e1e3104c14043b6ab86986926211276"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the girl ............................... sells books?",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses, that can refer to people in an informal style.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ea557f35ea046fa8ea5465881d04096"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is Janaki ................................. sells tickets?",
            "description": "That cannot be used in non-identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b1980e51f6e456b9a264e8b2c2061b7"
        }
    ]
}